thefoundation.io 2015-03-19

# The Foundation - Privacy Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address,  
phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

* * *

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

\- To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason  
whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

\- To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in  
addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the  
bottom of each email.

* * *

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access  
your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL)  
technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our  
systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than  
60 days in order to complete the 6 month period. .

* * *

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser  
(if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain  
information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data  
about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

* * *

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted  
third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to  
keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with  
the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor  
information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

* * *

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information  
from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or  
older.

* * *

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

* * *

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of  
our website at http://thefoundation.io/disclaimer

* * *

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

* * *

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on July 25, 2013

* * *

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://thefoundation.io

5600 Ashworth Road  
West Des Moines, IA 50266  
USA  
dane@thefoundation.io  
(515) 999-0485
